http://www.jboats.com/privacy-policy

(40.0')J/122E
(40.0')Other J/ModelsNewsJ/NewsletterJ/News ArticlesSubscribeSailing CalendarWall Calendar 2020J/Net BrokerageResourcesJ/Classes & OwnersJ/Gear StoreJ/Parts & EquipmentJ/Owner ResourcesJ/World Sailing SchoolContact UsRequest Brochure/InfoFind My DealerContact J/BoatsContact J/CompositesLicensed Builders
Menu
HomeBoatsCurrent J/ModelsJ/70
(22.8')J/80
(26.3')J/88
(29.2')J/97E
(31.5')J/99
(32.6')J/111
(36.5')J/112E
(36.0')J/121
(40.0')J/122E
(40.0')Other J/ModelsNewsJ/NewsletterJ/News ArticlesSubscribeSailing CalendarWall Calendar 2020J/Net BrokerageResourcesJ/Classes & OwnersJ/Gear StoreJ/Parts & EquipmentJ/Owner ResourcesJ/World Sailing SchoolContact UsRequest Brochure/InfoFind My DealerContact J/BoatsContact J/CompositesLicensed Builders
J/Boats Privacy Policy
Effective- as of May 25th, 2018
BasicsThis Privacy Policy is intended to inform the users of this website about the nature, scope and purpose of the collection and use of personal data by J/Boats Inc (a Connecticut Corporation) and its related licensees, data partners, and electronic services.We take your privacy very seriously and treat your personal information confidentially and in accordance with the law. As changes to this Privacy Policy may be made through new technologies and the continued evolution of this site, we encourage you to review the Privacy Policy periodically.Definitions of the terms used (e.g. “personal data” or “processing”) can be found in Article 4- GDPR.
Responsibility and Data Protection OfficerThe entity responsible for the processing of your data through this website is:
J/Boats Inc557 Thames St.Newport, RI 02840USAPhone- +1-401-846-8410Email- This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.You can reach our data protection officer via the email address This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Data PrivacyThe use of our website is possible without providing personal information. With regards to how we collect personal data (for example name, address or email addresses), this takes place, as far as possible, always on a voluntary basis. These data will not be disclosed to third parties without your explicit consent.Please note that data transmission over the Internet (for example, when communicating via email) may have security vulnerabilities. A complete protection of the data from access by third parties is not possible.
CookiesWe use cookies to facilitate and improve your visit on our website. The use of cookies constitutes a legitimate interest on our part. The legal basis for this is Article 6- GDPR.Popular browsers offer the preference option of not allowing cookies. Note: There is no guarantee that you will be able to access all the functions of this website without restrictions if you make the appropriate settings.
Collection and Processing of Personal DataPersonal data will only be collected by us and only to the extent that you provide us.  For example, in the context of a boat purchase, inquiry, brochure request, email newsletter registration, or J/Boat owner website, your personal data may be stored electronically, physically on paper, or via contracted data services.  You may see the J/Boats Privacy Policy Roadmap here on this link (a PDF document). Personal information means all information that is used to identify your person and which can be traced back to you – such as your name, email address, physical address and telephone number.This data is kept confidential and used only for the original purpose. Basically, the data is never transmitted to third parties. Unless it is required, or permitted by law, you have given us your consent or an official order has been made to store your personal data solely for the use by J/Boats.If you contact us via email, phone, or mail, the emails and the related data will be stored with us in the mail system, in the CRM (customer relations management system), or physically on paper. The legal basis for this is either Article 6- GDPR.The emails themselves are not encrypted.
Newsletter DataIf you would like to receive the newsletter offered on the website, we need an email address from you, as well as information that allows us to verify that you are the owner of the specified email address and that you agree to receive the newsletter. Further data is not collected. We use this data exclusively for the delivery of the requested information and do not pass it on to third parties.The newsletter is sent by MailChimp, 675 Ponce de Leon Avenue NE, Suite 5000, Atlanta, GA 30308 USA. For information about the privacy practices of the shipping service provider, please visit: https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/.Withdrawal and termination: You can revoke your consent to receive the newsletter at any time and thus cancel the newsletter subscription. After your cancellation, the deletion of your personal data takes place. Your consent to the newsletter shipping expires at the same time. At the end of each newsletter you will find the link to termination.
Privacy Policy for use of FacebookOn our pages, plugins of the social network Facebook, provider Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA, are integrated. The Facebook plugins recognize you by the Facebook logo or the terms “Like” on our site. An overview of the Facebook plugins can be found here: http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/.Facebook Inc. complies with European data protection law and is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement: https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=ActiveThe plugin creates a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook servers. The website operator has no influence whatsoever on the nature and extent of the data transmitted by the plugin to the Facebook Inc. servers. Information can be found here: https://www.facebook.com/help/186325668085084The plugin informs Facebook Inc. that you as a user have visited this website. There is the possibility that your IP address will be saved. If you are logged into your Facebook account while visiting this website, the information will be linked to it.If you use the functions of the plugin – for example by sharing or “liking” a post – the corresponding information will also be transmitted to Facebook Inc.If you want to prevent the Facebook Inc. associates to access this information with your Facebook account, please log out of Facebook before visiting this website and delete your stored cookies. Through your Facebook profile, you can make additional data processing settings for advertising purposes or object to the use of your data for promotional purposes. You can find the settings here:    Profile settings on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen    Cookie deactivation page on the US website: http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/        Cookie deactivation page on the European website: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/What data, for what purpose, and to what extent Facebook collects, uses and processes data and which rights and setting options you have to protect your privacy can be found in the Facebook Privacy Policy. These can be found here: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/
Privacy Policy for use of Google AnalyticsThis website uses functions of the web analytics service Google Analytics. The Provider is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”. These are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.Google LLC complies with European data protection law and is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement: https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=ActiveHowever, if IP anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will be shortened by Google beforehand within member states of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases the full IP address will be sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there.On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services related to website activity and Internet usage to the website operator. The IP address provided by Google Analytics as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other Google data.You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software.  However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use all the features of this website to the fullest extent possible. In addition, you may prevent the collection by Google of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading the browser plug-in available under the following link and install: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=enHere’s more information on data usage by Google Inc.:    https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners?hl=en (data collected by Google Partners)    https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated (settings about ads you see)        https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=en (use of cookies in ads)
Privacy Policy for use of InstagramFunctions of the service Instagram are integrated on our sites. These features are provided by Instagram Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA, 94025, United States. If you are logged in to your Instagram account, you can link the contents of our pages to your Instagram profile by clicking on the Instagram button. This allows Instagram to associate the visit to our pages with your user account. We point out that we as the provider of the pages do not receive knowledge of the content of the transmitted data and their use by Instagram.For more information, see the Instagram Privacy Policy: http://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/
Privacy Policy for use of TwitterFunctions of the Twitter service are integrated on our sites. These features are available through Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA. By using Twitter and the “Re-Tweet” function, the websites you visit are linked to your Twitter account and shared with other users. This data is also transmitted to Twitter.We point out that we as the provider of the pages are not aware of the content of the transmitted data and their use by Twitter. For more information, see the Twitter Privacy Policy at http://twitter.com/privacy.You can change your privacy settings on Twitter in the Account Settings at http://twitter.com/account/settings
Your RightsAt any time you have the right to information according to Article 15- GDPR, whether we process personal data from you. If this is the case, further information obligations on our part arise from this.Furthermore, you have the right to correct the data according to Article 16- GDPR, to delete the data according to Article 17- GDPR and to restrict the processing of the data according to Article 18- GDPR, if this is not precluded by further statutory provisions.Of course, you can use your given consent in accordance with Article 6- GDPR to revoke the data. This does not affect the legality of the processing until revocation.In addition, you are entitled to data transferability under Article 21- GDPR.In addition, in particular in the case of processing on the basis of Article 6- GDPR, you have the right under Article 20- GDPR to object to the processing of the data.You also have a right of appeal to the supervisory authority.
J/Boats’ RightsWe reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time, subject to applicable data protection laws.Effective- as of May 25th, 2018
J/Sailing Models
Current Models Classic J/Models Sailing Calendar
About J/Boats
History
Year by Year Review
The J/ DifferenceSpritboat RevolutionPHRF Ratings
Customer Service
Contact Us
Owner Resources
Request Information
Subscribe to J/News
Privacy Policy   |   Site Map   |   Get J/Boats Mobile App
© Copyright 2020 J/Boats, Inc. PO Box 90 Newport, RI 02840   +1 401-846-8410   This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
